How the West Was Fun is a family, western, drama
film directed by Stuart Margolin.
Twin sisters help a woman save her dude ranch from developers who
would like to turn the property into a theme park.
Susie Martin, played by Mary-Kate Olsen.
Jessica Martin, played by Ashley Olsen.
Bart Gafooley, played by Martin Mull.
Laura Forester, played by Michele Greene.
Stephen Martin, played by Patrick Cassidy.
George, played by Ben Cardinal.
How the West Was Fun is a 1994 American contemporary western television film starring
Mary-Kate and Ashley Olsen, with their sister Elizabeth in her film debut.
The film premiered on ABC on November 19, 1994.
The tone is emotional.